35.
Input:1.0, 5.1, 2.4, 7.2, 5.3
Output: 1.0, 2.4, 7.2, 5.3

37.
[(x < y)'V odd(n)] V [(x < y)' Λ odd(n)] => S(a)
[[(x < y)'V odd(n)] V [(x < y)' Λ odd(n)]]' => S(b)
	
38.Yes, the program executes correctly 

61.Percival is a truth teller, Llewellyn is a liar. If Percival is a telling the truth then, Llewellyn is the liar,
if he is lying then his statement is true which it cant be if he only lies.  

62.Merlin is a truth teller, Meredith is a truth teller. Merlyn's statement only says that meredith is a truth teller
Merlyn lying doesn't change anything about his statement, because it is only possible to evaluate if he says the truth. 

63.Rothwold is telling the truth, Grymlin is a truth teller as well. Rothwold says he is either a liar or grymlin is a truth teller,
if Rothwold is a liar then Grymlin cant be a truth teller based on his statement. if he is telling the truth then he 
is not a liar and thus Grymlin is a truth teller. 

64.Gwendolyn is a liar and so is Merrilaine. Gwendolyn says she is a liar, and this is true but only if she is lying about marrilaine
being a truth teller.
